Nanami-san!
That octopus currently thinks our
domains are pushing for control.
But my goal is different.
I'll open a small hole
in the barrier of this domain!
The hole I entered through
is already sealed.
It's harder to open one
from inside than outside,
but I can open a hole large enough for
someone to pass through for a few seconds.
The edge of his domain is beneath my feet.
I can tell, since I touched it when I entered.
I'm ready to go at any time!
If all three of you jump in at once...
None of this leaving yourself
behind alone, all right?
I'm risking my life,
but I don't intend to throw it away.
Episode 39
Fluctuations, Part 2
You two!
Gather 'round!
They faced an enemy
that understood language.
And with faith in their fellow grade-1
indirectly conveying his intentions,
the previously excluded possibility
of escaping the domain became
an option once more.
They're bolstering their defense of the boy?
That just groups them up for me to—
No!
He figured it out?! But it's too late!
To Fushiguro-kun's feet!
One who had inherited the curse
of the Zen'in clan from birth,
and one who could not
completely cast off that curse,
both stood in witness
to the one who cast it all off
now manifested in raw flesh...
and taking action.
Who's that?!
A person?
A sorcerer?
They brought a new sorcerer
in instead of escaping?
He's fast! He was just in mid-air!
That's not all, either!
What's with his strength?!
Maki-san!
I didn't feel any cursed energy from him!
Did I just lose a contest of pure strength?!
Me, of all people?!
Fushiguro-kun?
It's no good.
The hole has been sealed.
To make things worse,
it just figured out our goal.
It won't let us open a hole as easily again.
Toji!
Granny Ogami's seance technique
still continued after her death.
Her summoning of the dead
should have ceased
once her grandson, the vessel,
ran out of cursed energy.
But there was no cursed energy
in the grandson's soul
that was overwritten by Toji Zen'in's body,
and his body never expended
cursed energy, either.
Her technique had lost
its chance to terminate.
The compounding irregularities
left her technique running rampant,
and Toji Zen'in was currently
fighting as directed
by his instincts until his
vessel ultimately broke.
He had become a murder machine.
This man...
has no cursed energy?
Not worth my attention, then.
His fangs were constantly
directed toward the strongest.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Old man,
who is that?
A ghost.
Fushiguro-kun, can you
hold out a little longer?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
We're placing our bets on him.
He's smashing Playful Cloud against itself?
He's changing its shape...
Is he sharpening it?!
Am I going to lose?
Against a human with no cursed energy?!
No!
I can feel that young
boy's domain weakening!
If I can regain my guaranteed-hit
effect, I can kill them all!
I need to...
buy time!
Of course, you can hover, too, right?
Do I need to say it again?
It's not...
over yet!
The domain!
He seriously exorcised
that octopus all by himself!
If Fushiguro-kun hadn't come,
we all would've been wiped out for sure.
Though problems still remain.
Is he an ally or not?
Huh?
When did I get forced outside?
This goes beyond just fast!
He might be worse than Sukuna!
What is with this guy?!
Megumi!
You've passed on, Dagon?
Hey, hey, hey!
You're kidding, right?
This one's another level stronger...
Leave the rest to me.
...than that cursed spirit, Dagon!
Our souls will reincarnate,
even without relying on human beings.
Let us meet again in the
wasteland a century from now.
Now, then.
First one down.
Nana—
Second one down.
Third one down.
Sukuna?
No, it's not!
The fingers!
Someone has released Sukuna's
fingers somewhere here in Shibuya!
Let's hurry, Nanako.
The fingers might draw cursed spirits here.
I know.
Please,
come out,
Sukuna-sama.
You two! How many fingers did you feed him?!
I won't tell!
Mimiko!
That so? Then die.
Good, the markings haven't disappeared.
This was an unexpected turn of events,
but I'll make use of it to greatest effect.
Yuji Itadori probably wouldn't
transfer control of his body to Sukuna
even after taking in all 20 fingers.
But that's only if he spent
20 days taking one in every day.
If he took in ten at once,
his body wouldn't be able
to adapt quickly enough,
and control would transfer to Sukuna,
even if only temporarily.
Wake up,
Sukuna!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
I fed him all ten.
Now there should be at least
15 fingers inside Itadori.
You're alive?
Must have been the technique of one of them.
But given how frightened they are,
I doubt they can stop me that many times.
Don't waste my time!
I'll give you one second.
Move.
This is Sukuna...
Strength of a different kind than Satoru Gojo!
Overwhelming evil!
Fear that even the slightest
move could lead to death!
Breathe!
Breathe, breathe!
Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe!
It's okay to breathe, right?
He won't kill us for that, right?
You hold your heads quite high.
Did you believe taking one knee was enough?
The greatest men bow
the lowest, or so it goes.
I see you value your head quite lightly.
You brats,
I'll start with you.
You wished to speak to me, yes?
I'll grant you a finger's worth of audience.
Now speak.
B-Below us, there's a man in monk's robes
with a suture across his forehead.
P-Please kill him.
Please free Geto-sama.
Hey, Geto-sama?
Who is Satoru Gojo?
He's super strong, right?
Well...
He was my best friend.
But we had a fight and haven't spoken since.
I love you.
We'll never forgive Satoru Gojo for
killing Geto-sama, so long as we live.
But we did feel that was appropriate.
After all,
Satoru Gojo was Geto-sama's
one and only best friend.
But you are different.
Go to hell!
We'll make you regret this!
We know the location of one other finger.
If you'll kill that man for us,
we'll tell you where it is.
So please...
Raise your heads.
Mimiko! Mimiko! Mimiko!
Did you think a measly one or two fingers
Mimiko! Mimiko!
would grant you the right to order me around?
No! Mimiko!
No way, no way!
Mimiko! Mimiko!
How offensive.
Mimiko!
Sukuna!
Die!
Hmm, a cell phone?
No, the photo function, huh?
It was probably some ability to do something
to whatever was pictured in the photo.
Boring.
You're next, cursed spirit.
What do you want?
I want...
nothing!
What?
Our objective, Sukuna,
is your complete resurrection.
Currently, you only have temporary freedom
while Itadori struggles to adapt.
I'm sure you're the most
aware of that yourself.
Even if Sukuna's Reverse Cursed Technique
is capable of healing others as well,
it can't do anything about the shape of
a soul once it's changed by
Mahito's Idle Transfiguration.
It wasn't that he didn't forge a pact back then.
It was that he couldn't.
Forge a pact with Yuji Itadori
before he returns!
A pact to grant you perpetual
authority over his body!
Many of Itadori's allies are already here.
There are plenty of ways you could do it.
There's no need.
I already have my own plans.
But I see...
You all are desperate, too.
This is your reward for the fingers. Come at me.
If you manage to land even
a single blow on me,
I'll work under you all.
For starters, how about
I slaughter every human in Shibuya?
Except for one.
You're true to your word, yes?
If you're going to use jujutsu,
you should do it like this!
Um, there are minors present.
Barrier! Technique! One, two, shoot!
Please, students are watching.
I threw out paper, so all
of you who threw scissors
might see something
good happening tomorrow!
Please don't suddenly try
to make this kid-friendly.
Next Episode
Thunderclap
Next time, "Thunderclap."
I'm so drunk!